cartoonnetworkme.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting [www.CartoonNetworkMe.com](http://www.cartoonnetworkme.com/ "Link: http://www.cartoonnetworkme.com") \- a site operated by Turner Broadcasting System Europe Limited (“TBSEL”, “we” or “us”). This Privacy Policy explains how we use information we collect about you and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. Please take the time to read the full Privacy Policy. By using this site, including when you access any content, subscribe to any service or otherwise contact us for any reason, you consent to the data collection, use and disclosure practices described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may be subject to separate or additional data protection notices presented at the point of data collection.   

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, any reference to “parent” shall include legal guardian.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT 

At some of our web pages, you can order products, enter competitions, upload and communicate information, such as comments, ideas, photos, drawings, images, videos, artwork, sound recordings or other materials (“End User Content”), vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion,  contact us if you have any query,  subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums, or  communities. 

The types of information that may be collected at these pages include: your name, screen name, password, e-mail address, postal address, telephone/mobile number, your gender, country of residence and date of birth. We request these details in order to provide the service or product to you (i.e. despatch prizes, send goodies via email or post), to respond to any queries you may have, and to ensure we request and receive the correct consent from you or your parents.

We may ask you for other information, including, but not limited to, your interests, opinions and the way you use our services to assist us in our initiatives and to improve our understanding of user trends and patterns.

If you are under sixteen and participate in an activity that requires the collection and retention of your personal information to allow for continued recognition or registration for a particular functionality , we will also ask for your parent’s e-mail address so that we can obtain your parent’s permission to process your personal information. We do not knowingly collect names and e-mail addresses from anyone under sixteen for these types of activities without notifying their parents via e-mail and giving that parent the option to consent to their child’s personal details being included in the applicable database for that activity. During the period when parental consent is being requested, your account will be held in our database on a temporary basis. If we do not receive your parent’s consent we will delete the information provided by you within a reasonable period of time in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

If we collect your personal information to allow you to enter a competition, or other similar one-time activities the specific terms for participating in that activity will provide you with additional information about the collecting and processing of this information.

At some of our web pages, you may be able to submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card and, if you order a gift on-line and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient's name and home address. The types of information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, and e-mail address. We will only use this information to provide the product or service as requested.  We ask that you ensure that you obtain any person’s consent before providing their personal details and that you do not provide information regarding anyone under the age of eighteen unless you are their parent.  

USE OF INFORMATION

For specific one-time requests we receive from visitors, e-mail addresses are collected and used only in connection with the specific one-time request.

We use visitors' personal information collected in connection with our activities for internal purposes only, such as reporting, enabling visitors to enter our online competitions, submit their End User Content or subscribe to our online newsletter, providing the service or product requested, providing  customer service and/or for the specific purpose for which the information was provided. 

We may also use the information for other purposes disclosed to visitors at the time their information is collected.

We use parents' e-mail addresses provided by children to notify them when we have received personal information such as e-mail addresses from their children and to give parents the option to remove their child's name from our lists. 

We keep any personal information we obtain through a competition for the time necessary to successfully select winners, award the prizes, and administer the competition. 

APPS

We may offer games and other downloadable applications (commonly referred to as "Apps") through various third party platforms (such as Apple's iTunes App Store, Google Play, etc.). Our Apps generally include features, functionality and content such as games, videos, and activities. TBSEL does not knowingly collect personal  information from children under the age of 16 through our Apps. The data collected in an App may vary by App but will include any information a user provides once the user downloads and uses the App. For example, some of our Apps may require you to first register and create an account with us (e.g. user name, password, or email address) before you can use it. Other Apps may require additional information from you, such as transaction-related information (e.g. when you make purchases, respond to any offers). We may also use information you provide us to reach you when you contact us for help. If you interact with third-party social media sites and applications, we may have access to certain information from your social media account such as your user name, profile picture, information about friends and followers, and content posted or viewed through the social media. When you use social media networking platforms and plugins, you share your information with them and their use of the information will be subject to that social media site’s privacy practices. To help improve the design, functionality, performance, and content of our Apps, we usually collect certain information when you use the App on your mobile device, such as usage, viewing and technical data including the type of mobile device you use, your unique device ID, your device’s IP address, your mobile operator and operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the App. Our Apps usually do not collect precise information about the location of your mobile device, and only would do so if you are specifically prompted to provide your consent to do so. You can always manage your location preferences at any time by adjusting the settings on your device. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with any personally identifiable information through an App without consent, please contact us at [apps.emea@turner.com](mailto:apps.emea@turner.com "Link: mailto:apps.emea@turner.com") so we can delete such information.

 COOKIES

When you visit this site we send "cookies" to your computer primarily to enhance your on-line experience. "Cookies" are small files which can identify your terminal equipment and store your personal preferences as well as technical information. 

We use cookies and technical information to personalise your visit to our site (e.g., to recognise you by name when you return to our site) and understand your trends. This helps us improve the design and content of our site for visitors and assists us in our marketing initiatives.

Certain areas of our site use cookies for a specific reason, for example, to help an online game work effectively. Most web browsers allow you to control how cookies are put on your computer  and you can set them at any time to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, please note that some parts of this site may not function properly if you refuse cookies. For more information on cookies and how to disable them you can consult our [Cookies Policy](http://www.cartoonnetworkme.com/cookies-policy "Link: http://www.cartoonnetworkme.com/cookies-policy"). 

DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

We may share information about visitors to this site in aggregate with third parties including advertisers, business partners, and sponsors, to understand user trends and patterns and manage and improve our business relationships. Please be assured that such information will be anonymised so that your identity is protected.

We may disclose your personal data to affiliates, third party providers, contractors and partners for the purposes listed in this Privacy Policy. In particular, we may share personal information with third parties to administer and process your requests (e.g., when you order a product or service we may share your details with third party financial institutions to process payment for your order). We may also share your details with third parties (such as auditors or legal advisors) to obtain professional advice.

Agents and contractors who have access to personal information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, in particular, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing.

We may disclose personal information we hold in response to legal proceedings, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We may also disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of our terms of use or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer personally identifiable information about you if we or one of our business units are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another entity.

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

Some of our sites contain links to other sites where information practices may be different to ours. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" may take you off this web site. This includes links from advertisers, channel sponsors and partners that may use our logos as part of a co-branding agreement. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we are not responsible for and have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

We sometimes may offer content (e.g., competitions, prize draws, or promotions) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personal information that you voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. We are not responsible for and have no control over these third parties' use of this information. However, we will notify you at the time of requesting personal information if these third parties will obtain such information.

We may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at this site (please refer to our Cookies Policy [hyperlink] for more details). This Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party ad server may have collected from you. 

CONTACT AND NOTICES 

Although absolute security cannot be guaranteed on the Internet, please be assured that we have in place security measures to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. We will continue to maintain and improve these measures over time in line with legal and technological developments.

You can contact us at any time at [privacy.arabic@turner.com](mailto:privacy.arabic@turner.com) to see the personal information we have collected through this site which relates to you, and in some cases, your children, and to ask us to make any necessary changes to correct or update your information. To protect your privacy and security we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access.

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, the changes will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will not use or disclose personal information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without informing you and providing you with an opportunity to opt-out of these unrelated uses.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy please feel free to contact us at [privacy.arabic@turner.com](mailto:privacy.arabic@turner.com).

PARENTAL GUIDANCE

It is important to us that children can enjoy our sites in a responsible fashion. We, therefore, encourage children to consult with their parents before providing personal information. We also encourage parents to supervise their children's online activities by, for example, adopting parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personal information without parental permission.

Cartoon Network Online   
Turner Broadcasting System Europe Limited   
16 Great Marlborough Street   
London   
W1F 7HS   
England   
(registered office: Turner House, 16 Great Marlborough Street, London, W1F 7HS) 

3 July 2015
